I never imagined that my sisters would play such a dirty prank on me.  I was going
out for some work in Darshan when
suddenly my mother caught me.   He is
travelling a lot these days.  Come get the housework done.
I said, mom, get it done by your sisters.
She is getting ready.
Ready for what?  I will go and see right now.  Now
as soon as I came to my room.  Both of them got
ready and were busy doing makeup.
Hey brother, where are you going so ready?
At the birthday party.  If you want to go, get ready quickly.   I will be back in just
two minutes.  Now I was getting ready and
looking in the mirror when my mother
came and said,
hey hero, first look at your face.
How much tan has he got in the sun.   Do
n't worry about that mom because I
use Maharth Octa Natural Glow
Face Wash.  It contains turmeric and saffron which
remove tan and give a
natural glow to the skin and the best part is that it is
completely safe to apply.  Now brother, you are ready.
I told my sister, let's get
in the car and leave for the party.  But
then my sisters stopped the car and said that
we have reached our destination.  Hey, it was a birthday
party, right?   It's
not a happy birthday party, it's a happy prank.
What do you mean?
You scared us with a snake.  Today the item was completed.
Now tell me what should be done with them?
I will look at these.  If you want the product, please
tag above.